Okay, whatever. This is the tool. I think you're pretty familiar with it now. I do not want to
spend no more time on it because I assume that it is pretty clear.
I just want to click on view all tools just to see what we have. Wow.
Wow, there's plenty of them.
Okay, there's actually a lot of them.
All tools. So we have tools for writing, education, business, marketing, and other.
And we can even search over here, right? For the very tool that we want. So we have email
responder, you know, so it's specifically for an email and we'll copy the email and paste it over
here. And then we'll ask for a response, right? So that's exactly what it will do for us.
What else do we have? We have rewrite content. We have expert writing assistant. We have all of
these tools over here available. And we can use any of them that we want, right?
There's actually a lot of them. Look, they're a lot. I really wanted to know
the exact number of these, but I assume there's no way that I can understand that. But whatever,